Toni Morrison Papers, 1908-2017: Finding Aid C1491
mss EADs that duplicate ones in Manuscripts
- Photographs, 1949-2015; 17 boxes
  - The Links, Inc., 1986; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 12)
    3 color photographs; letter from Antonia W. Gary, Greater Miami United. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Toni Gary, Dianne Saulney Smith, Al Dotson, Marilyn Hallified, Regina Frazier.
  - Literary Week Proclamation, New York City, 1981; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 13)
    1 color photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Ed Koch, Judith Appelbaum.
  - Lorain Chamber of Commerce Annual Meeting and President's Ball, 1982 January 15; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 14)
    3 color photographs, 4 black and white photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Ella Ramah Wofford. Includes letter from John G. Cole, dated Dec. 20, 1985.
  - Lorain High School Yearbook Pages, 1949; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 15)
    4 black and white reproductions of yearbook pages.
  - Yo Yo Ma Concert, 2001 March 17; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 16)
    4 color photographs.
  - Nelson Mandela, undated; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 17)
  - Margaret Garner Essay Contest Winners, 2006 April 27; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 18)
    Pictured: Teresa Robertson, Toni Morrison, and student essay contest winners.
  - Margaret Garner Opera Carolina Scrapbook, circa 2006; 1 box (Box 263)
  - Margaret Garner Premier, Cincinnati, 2005 July 5; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 19)
    2 color printouts. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Richard Danielpour.
  - Melcher Book Award, 1988; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 20)
  - Mexico, undated; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 21)
    3 slides.
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, 2015; 1 folder (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Slade Morrison, 1987 November; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 22)
  - Toni Morrison, Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, and Etan Thomas, 2007; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 23)
    2 color photographs; sent from Deborah Morales.
  - Toni Morrison Birthday Party, 1991 February; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 24)
  - Toni Morrison Birthday Party, 1993 February; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 25)
    24 color photographs. Pictured: Kevin Gaines, Paula Giddings, Wahneema Lubiano, Erroll McDonald, Toni Morrison, Al Rabateau, Arnold Rampersad, Cornel West, Marvina White, and others.
  - Toni Morrison, Black Oak Books, Berkeley, 1987; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 26)
    1 photograph, black and white; exhibition announcement and letter from Lynda Koolish, dated 2001.
  - Toni Morrison and Bill Clinton, 1993 September 14; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 27)
    1 color photograph signed by Bill Clinton; letter from Ann Stock, White House Social Secretary, dated October 19, 1993.
  - Toni Morrison and Bill Clinton, Aspen Ideas Festival, 2005 July 7; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 28)
    2 color printouts.
  - Toni Morrison and Hillary Clinton, Bicentennial of the Library of Congress Tea, 1997 October 7; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 29)
    2 color photographs and letter from White House Social Secretary.
  - Toni Morrison and Angela Davis, New York City, 1974; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 30)
    3 photocopies, black and white.
  - Toni Morrison and David Dinkins, 1993 November; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 31)
    4 color photographs. Also pictured: Kurt Vonnegut, Anne Thompson.
  - Toni Morrison and Yvonne Divans-Hutchinson, Los Angeles, 1997 July 27; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 32)
  - Toni Morrison and Editorial Germania Editor, 1999 October 19; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 33)
    2 color photographs.
  - Toni Morrison and Helen Frankenthaler, 1989 January 19; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 34)
    1 black and white photograph; letter from Helen Frankenthaler.
  - Toni Morrison and Phyllis Franklin, 1989; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 35)
    1 color photograph and letter from Phyllis Franklin, dated August 26, 1989.
  - Toni Morrison with Barrett and Nonnie Frelinghuysen, undated; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 36)
    1 color photograph. Taken at the Marie and Edward Matthews '53 Acting Studio, Princeton University.
  - Toni Morrison and Friends, Lorain, Ohio, 1990 August; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 37)
  - Toni Morrison and Friends, Ohio Theatre, Columbus, Ohio, undated; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 38)
    1 color photoraph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Lois Wofford Books.
  - Toni Morrison and Vartan Gregorian, New York Public Library, 1989; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 39)
  - Toni Morrison, Holt, Rinehart & Winston Bluest Eye Promo Photo, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 40)
    6 black and white photographs. 1 signed by Morrison.
  - Toni Morrison and Charlayne Hunter-Gault, undated; 1 folder (Box 252, Folder 41)
  - Toni Morrison, Italy, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 1)
    11 color photographs. Also pictured: Carla Tanzi.
  - Toni Morrison, Knopf Beloved Promo Photos, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 2)
    3 photographs and contact sheet, black and white.
  - Toni Morrison, Knopf Jazz Promo Photos, 1991; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 3)
    10 photographs, black and white. With Jazz publicity cards and note from Knopf Promotion Department.
  - Toni Morrison, Knopf Jazz and Paradise Promo Photos, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 4)
    8 black and white photographs.
  - Toni Morrison, Knopf Promo Photos, 1983; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 5)
    Black and white photographs. With note from Joshua S. Odell.
  - Toni Morrison, Knopf Song of Solomon Promo Photos, 1978; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 3)
    3 black and white photographs and negative with letter from Nicholas Latimer at Knopf; 1 black and white photograph with letter from Helen Marcus dated December 9, 2013.
  - Toni Morrison, Knopf Sula Promo Photos, circa 1973; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 6)
    11 photographs, black and white.
  - Toni Morrison, Knopf Tar Baby Promo Photo, 1981; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Toni Morrison and Jhumpa Lahiri, circa 1995; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Toni Morrison and Sonny Mehta, 52nd Presidential Inaugural, 1993; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - Toni Morrison, Miscellaneous Photos, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 10)
  - Toni, Ford, and Slade Morrison, undated; 1 folder 1 black and white printout. (Box 253, Folder 11)
  - Toni and Slade Morrison, Spring Valley, New York, 1978; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 12)
  - Toni and Slade Morrison, Who's Got Game? Promo Photos, circa 2003; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 13)
    3 color printouts.
  - Toni Morrison, New York City Apartment, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 14)
  - Toni Morrison and Mary Lovelace O'Neal, Paris, 1993; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 15)
  - Toni Morrison with Frank and Joan Owens, 1988; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 16)
    9 color photographs. With letter from Joan Owens, dated Nov. 11, 1988. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Slade Morrison, Frank Owens, and Joan Owens. Taken at Toni Morrison's house in Grand View on Hudson, New York.
  - Toni Morrison with Oprah Winfrey, Angela Davis, Maya Angelou, and Others, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 32)
    6 black-and-white photographs, inscribed in the corner by "Eugene."
  - Toni Morrison in Paris, Hôtel des Saints-Pères, 1985 January; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 17)
    1 photograph, black and white; postcard from Chantal Regnault.
  - Toni Morrison Passport Photo, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 18)
    1 negative.
  - Toni Morrison and Gayle Pemberton, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 19)
  - Toni Morrison Portrait by Colita, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 20)
    1 black and white photograph, with note from "B" at The New Yorker.
  - Toni Morrison Portrait by Nancy Crampton, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 21)
    2 printouts; 1 black and white, 1 color.
  - Toni Morrison Portrait by Bernard Gotfryd, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 22)
    1 black and white photograph proof.
  - Toni Morrison Portrait by Timothy Greenfield-Sanders, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 23)
    1 color printout.
  - Toni Morrison Portrait by Timothy Greenfield-Sanders for Vanity Fair, 2008; 1 box (Box 262)
    1 color photograph, with card from Graydon Carter.
  - Toni Morrison Portrait by Annie Leibovitz, undated; 1 box (Box 262)
    1 black and white printout.
  - Toni Morrison Portraits by Digne Meller Marcovicz, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 24)
    9 black and white photographs.
  - Toni Morrison Portraits by Maria Mulas, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 25)
    6 black and white photographs.
  - Toni Morrison Portraits, Princeton University, 1997; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 26)
    29 photographs, 2 contact sheets, and letter from Princeton Development Communications Office. Also pictured: Ellen Goellner.
  - Toni Morrison Portrait, Rolex Mentor and Protege Arts Initiative, 2005; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 4)
    1 black and white photograph, with letter and notecard from Barbara Geary, Rolex Mentor and Protege Arts Initiative.
  - Toni Morrison Portraits by Unknown Photographers, undated; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 27)
    TK black and white photographs.
  - Toni Morrison Reading Room Dedication, Lorain Public Library, 1995 January 22; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 28)
    34 photographs, color and black and white.
  - Toni Morrison and Eugene B. Redmond; East St. Louis, Illinois, 1985 November; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 29)
    29 color photographs; note from Eugene B. Redmond, dated November 19, 1985.
  - Toni Morrison and Beah Richards, 1998 July 24; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 30)
    1 black and white photograph; letter from S. Pearl Sharp dated September 4, 1998.
  - Toni Morrison and Liz Rohatyn, New York Public Library, 1987 October; 1 folder (Box 253, Folder 31)
    1 black and white photograph; letter from Jennifer Herring, Deputy Director, Campaign for the Library.
  - Toni Morrison, Joan Schulz's House, 1988 Spring; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 1)
    1 color photograph and note.
  - Toni Morrison and Peter Sellars, Princeton Atelier Performance, 1996 March 30; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Toni Morrison, Slam Poetry Night at the Louvre, 2006 November 10; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Toni Morrison and Wole Soyinka, undated; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 4)
    4 black and white photographs.
  - Toni Morrison, Stockholm, 1993 October; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 5)
    Inscribed from "Otto."
  - Toni Morrison, Toni Morrison Elementary School; Lorain, Ohio, undated; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - Toni Morrison, Tribeca Film Festival Dinner, 2002 May 7; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 7)
    1 color photograph and card from Graydon Carter.
  - Toni Morrison and Unidentified Woman, Topaz Hotel, undated; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 8)
  - Toni Morrison, Union Square, New York City, 2003 January 27; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 5)
    2 black and white photographs.
  - Toni Morrison, University of Wisconsin--Madison, 1990 February; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 6)
    2 black and white photographs, with letter from David Arons.
  - Toni Morrison and Joan Walker, 2004 December 10; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 9)
  - Toni Morrison, Joan Walker, and Anne Thompson, undated; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 10)
  - Toni Morrison, Cornel West, and Tavis Smiley, 2005 September 21; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 11)
  - Toni Morrison and Oprah Winfrey, Oprah's 50th Birthday Celebration, 2004 January; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 12)
  - Toni Morrison and Oprah Winfrey, The Oprah Winfrey Show, 1996; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 13)
    1 color photograph; letter from Olivia Gerth, Associate Producer, Oprah Winfrey Show. Song of Solomon Book Club.
  - Toni Morrison and Oprah Winfrey, The Oprah Winfrey Show, 2000; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 14)
    1 color photograph; letter from Amanda Casgar, Oprah Winfrey Show. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Oprah Winfrey.
  - Toni Morrison, Oprah Winfrey, and Harold and Vivian Shapiro, 1998; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 15)
    2 color photographs; notes from Oprah Winfrey Show and Robert K. Durkee, Princeton University.
  - Toni Morrison and Ella Ramah Wofford, 1981 December; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 16)
  - Toni Morrison, Ella Ramah Wofford, and Rosemary DiFillipo; Lorain, Ohio, 1988 July; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 17)
    12 color photographs, 1 black and white photograph of Morrison's childhood home, with letter from Rosemary DiFillipo.
  - National Arts Club Award, 1999 February 2; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 18)
    13 black and white photographs, 1 color photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, O. Aldon James, Jr., Fran Lebowitz, Sonny Mehta, John Leonard, Erroll McDonald, Sue Leonard, Paul LeClerc, Marjory Bassett, Ford Morrison, Peter Carey.
  - National Book Award, 1999 November 17; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 19)
    1 color photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Oprah Winfrey.
  - National Book Award C-SPAN2 Broadcast, undated; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 20)
  - National Book Week, Borders, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1997; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 21)
    10 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Ford Morrison, Fran Lebowitz, Sonny Mehta, Eileen Ahearn.
  - National Humanities Medal, 2000 December 20; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 22)
    21 color photographs. Pictured: Bill Clinton, Barbara Kingsolver, Sonia Sanchez, Chris Madden, Toni Morrison, Barbra Streisand, Captain Dunn.
  - National Humanities Medal Official White House Photos, 2000 December 20; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 23)
    12 color photographs, with letter from Capricia Penavic Marshall, White House Social Secretary. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Bill Clinton.
  - National Middle School Association, Indianapolis, 1997; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 24)
  - Negro Ensemble Co. Party, 1982; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 25)
    1 black and white photograph; letter from Edward Burbridge dated March 30 1998. Pictured: Clinton Turner David, Lauren Jones, Jackee, Toni Morrison, Edward Burbridge, Billie Allen Henderson.
  - New York Public Library Corporate Dinner, 2000 June 19; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 26)
    1 color photograph; letter from Samuel Butler, Chairman of the Board. Pictured: Toni Morrison and Paul LeClerc.
  - New York Public Library Dinner, 1989 October 12; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 27)
    2 black and white photographs; note from Andrew [Heiskell], NYPL. Pictured: Barbara Bush, Toni Morrison, Tom Wolfe, William Styron.
  - New York Public Library Jubilee, 1986; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 28)
    4 black and white photographs; note from Gregory Long, Vice President, Public Affairs and Development, NYPL. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Vartan Gregorian.
  - New York Public Library Literary Lions Dinner, 1982 November 4; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 29)
    5 black and white photographs; letter from Vartan Gregorian dated April 11, 1983. Pictured: William F. Buckley, Jr., Lewis Thomas, Henry Kissinger, Isaac B. Singer, Barbara W. Tuchman, John Irving, Gail Godwin, Shirley Hazzard, Carlos Fuentes, Roger Angell, Robert K. Massie, Adam Smith, Toni Morrison, Isaac Asimov, Ralph Ellison, Francis Steegmuller.
  - New York Public Library Schomburg Center Founder's Day, 1986; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 30)
    1 black and white photograph; letter from Howard Dodson, Chief of the Schomburg Center, dated March 10, 1986. Pictured: Howard Dodson and Toni Morrison.
  - New York State Legislature Commendation, 1988 June 6; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 31)
    6 black and white photographs. Resolution 949 Commending Toni Morrison on Pulitzer Prize. Pictured: Toni Morrison, New York State Senator Manfred Ohrenstein.
  - Nobel Album, 1993; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 32)
    Album with 18 color photographs.
  - Nobel Celebration, Princeton NJ, 1993 October 7; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 33)
    2 color photographs; note from Arnold Rampersad. Pictured: Fran Lebowitz, Toni Morrison, Arnold Rampersad.
  - Nobel Dinner, Stockholm, 1993; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 7)
    Inscribed to Toni Morrison from Fritz [Cammerzell]. Pictured: Fritz Cammerzell, René Boatman, Henry Louis Gates, Elleni Gebre Amlak, Ford Morrison, Fran Lebowitz, Toni Morrison, Claudia Brodsky Lacour, Cornel West, Wole Soyinka, Vivian Shapiro, Dan Shepperd.
  - Nobel Laureates, Nobel Foundation, 1993 December; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 34)
    2 color photographs and letter from Kristina Fallenius, Nobel Foundation.
  - Nobel Laureates, Prisvärda Tankar Program, 1994; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 35)
  - Nobel Prize, 1993; 1 folder (Box 254, Folder 36)
    6 color photographs; letter from Jeppe Wikström, Pressens Bild.
  - Nobel Prize, 1993; 5 folders (Box 255, Folder 1-5)
    Approximately 110 color photographs, 11 black and white photographs. Includes photographs of the Prize ceremony and banquet, as well as various snapshots around Stockholm.
  - Northwestern University, undated; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 6)
    8 color photographs and notecard from Harry S. Bienen.
  - One City, One Book Gala, Vienna, 2006 November 19; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 7)
    10 color photographs; with note from Lorenz Giorgi, dated November 20, 2006.
  - Paradise Book Party, 1998; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 8)
    26 color photographs; card from Joan Walker, dated January 27, 1998. Pictured: David Dinkins, Joyce Dinkins, Toni Morrison, Joan Walker, and others.
  - Paradise Booksigning, 1998; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 9)
  - Paris, undated; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 10)
    5 pages color thumnail pictures, computer printout.
  - Pell Awards, 2001 April 27; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 11)
    2 color photographs, 1 black and white photograph, note from Chira DelSesto.
  - Photo Album, undated; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 12)
    Includes photos from multiple events. Pictured: Ellen Chances, Toni Morrison, Georgia Nugent, Al Raboteau, Ruth Simmons, Cornel West, John Willis, and others.
  - Nélida Piñon Bookstore Display, undated; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 13)
  - Pratt Society Lifetime Achievement Award, Baltimore MD, 2001; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 14)
    5 color photographs. Pictured: Lucille Clifton, Toni Morrison.
  - Princeton University 250th Anniversary Address, 1996 October; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 15)
  - Princeton University Commencement, 2002 June 4; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 16)
    2 color photographs and 2 tickets. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Oprah Winfrey.
  - Prospect House Dinner, Princeton University, undated; 1 folder (Box 255, Folder 17)
    18 color photographs.
  - David Rockefeller Dinner for Nelson Mandela, 1993 July 5; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 1)
    3 color photographs; letter from David Rockefeller.
  - Salman Rushdie Book Party, 2001 September 19; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 2)
    5 color photographs. Pictured: Derek Walcott, Toni Morrison, Padma Lakshmi.
  - Rutgers University Commencement, 2011; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 3)
    11 color photographs; letter from Leslie A. Fehrenbach, Secretary of the University.
  - Sara Lee Frontrunner Award, 1989; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 4)
    11 photographs, color and black and white; notecard from Sara Lee Corporate Affairs Department. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Maya Angelou, Mathilde Krim, Judith Lichtman.
  - Sarah Lawrence College Commencement, 1988; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 5)
    2 color photographs; letter from Alice Stone Ilchman dated June 16, 1988
  - Issaka Sawadogo, 1993 October; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - "Scarlett and Her Sisters: Race, Women and Literature," Collège de France, 1994 November 4; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 7)
    21 black and white photographs; card announcing lecture.
  - Ruth Simmons, 1999 May 27; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 8)
  - Ruth Simmons Inauguration, Smith College, 1995 October; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 9)
    21 color photographs.
  - Sistren: Black Women Writers at the Inauguration of Sister President Johnnetta B. Cole, 1988; 1 box (Box 262)
    1 color photograph. Pictured: Louise Meriwether, Pinkie Gordon Lane, Johnnetta B. Cole, Paula Giddings, Pearl Cleage, Gwendolyn Brooks, Toni Cade Bambara, Sonia Sanchez, Nikki Giovanni, Mari Evans.
  - Smith College Commencement, 1991; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 10)
    1 black and white photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison and Mary Maples Dunn.
  - Smith College Commencement, 2001; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 11)
    6 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Shelly Lazarus, Cornel West, Ruth Simmons.
  - Smith College Reading, 1995 September 30; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 12)
  - Sorbonne Cérémonie Honoris Causa, 2007 December 14; 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 13)
    16 color photographs, card.
  - Spelman College Reading, 1990 November 15; 2 folders (Box 256, Folder 14-15)
    Approximately 90 photographs, black and white and color; promotional notice for lecture and Susan J. Ross photocopied business card.
  - SUNY Albany Album and Scrapbook, 1987; 1 box (Box 264)
  - Syracuse University Visiting Professorship, 1988 October 5-26; 2 folders (Box 257, Folder 1-2)
    42 black and white photographs; 6 color photographs; press release and clippings.
  - Three City Cinema Reception, Oakland Musem, 1987 November 1; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 3)
    1 color photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Ishmael Reed, John Williams, and Guests.
  - Time Magazine 75th Anniversary Gala, 1998 March 3; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 4)
    1 color photograph, commemorative program, and note from Patrick McMullan. Pictured: Molly Ringwald, Toni Morrison, Jodie Foster.
  - Toni Morrison Society 70th Birthday Gala, NYPL, 2001 February 17; 2 boxes
    245 color photographs.
    - Toni Morrison Society 70th Birthday Gala, NYPL, 2001 February 17; 4 folders (Box 257, Folder 5-8)
    - Toni Morrison Society 70th Birthday Gala, NYPL, 2001 February 17; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Toni Morrison Society Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, 1998 September 23-27; 2 folders (Box 258, Folder 2-3)
    Approximately 70 color photographs; note from Carolyn Denard; conference program.
  - Toni Morrison Society Conference, Charleston, South Carolina, 2008; 3 folders (Box 258, Folder 4-6)
    Approximately 140 color photographs.
  - Toni Morrison Society Conference, Charleston, South Carolina, 2008; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 8)
    3 color photographs.
  - Toni Morrison Society Conference, Cincinnati, Ohio, 2005 July 14-17; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 7)
    13 color photographs.
  - Toni Morrison Society Conference, Northern Kentucky University, 2005 July 16-18; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 1)
    32 color photographs; letter from Bob Wallace, Northern Kentucky University.
  - Unidentified Photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - University of Michigan Commencement, 1992; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 3)
    8 color photographs; notecard from James J. Duderstadt. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Joyce Carol Oates.
  - University of Oxford Commencement, 2005 June 22; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 4)
    4 color photographs; note from Vice-Chancellor, University of Oxford.
  - University of Pennsylvania, 2004; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 5)
    19 color photographs; notecard from Amy Gutmann. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Amy Gutmann, and others.
  - University of Pennsylvania Scrapbook, 1988 May 16; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 9)
  - University of Toronto Honorary Degree, 2002 May 28; 2 folders (Box 259, Folder 6-7)
    Approximately color 75 photographs; letter from University of Toronto Office of the President.
  - University of Wisconsin--Madison Lecture, 1990 October; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 8)
    5 black and white photographs and photocopied press clippings.
  - Unwritten Love Letter #149, 1990; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 9)
  - Versailles, 1994 November 16; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute Lecture, 1988 May 5-6; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 11)
    3 color Polaroids.
  - Wake Forest University Commencement, 1997; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 12)
    3 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Maya Angelou.
  - Wellesley College Commencement, 2004; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 13)
    5 color photographs, card from Sue Newhouse.
  - Cornel West, Louise Archambault, William Greaves, Ruth Simmons, undated; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 14)
  - Cornel West Party, 1993; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 15)
    4 color photographs and note from Kevin Gaines. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Cornel West, Elleni Gebre Amlak.